Christopher Kelly

905-995-1105 ckelly.tor@gmail.com • chriskelly48th.ca Toronto, Ontario, M5R 1E9

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced team leader with emphasis on training and collaboration. Recent computer programming graduate focusing on front-end and back-end web development as well as cross-platform app development. Used to fast-paced work environments and focused on meeting deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ignite TV Customer Support

Sep 2018 - Mar 2019

Rogers • Toronto, Ontario

Provide customers with technical support over the phone and using diagnostic tools to solve technical issues

- Trained to support customers with a brand-new product
- · Part of the second wave of technical support specialists for IPTV
- Cross-trained to provide basic customer service and sales solutions

Retail Supervisor

Sep 2013 - Aug 2018

Best Buy • Ajax, Ontario

Responsible for merchandising and inventory management (Product Process Senior) / Responsible for training and increasing revenue in each department (Sales Senior)

- Increased productivity by providing weekly reports to management
- Recognized in company memo for providing exceptional customer service
- Chosen to help open a new store and train all new staff members (Oshawa)

Warehouse manager

Oct 2011 - Sep 2013

Leons

Hired as warehouse associate in Scarborough. Lead Inventory team and promoted to manager in Whitby six months later

- Plan, organize, direct, control and evaluate the operations of commercial, transportation and recreational facilities and the included real estate
- Plan, organize and direct administrative services such as signage, cleaning, maintenance, parking, safety inspections, security and snow removal
- Prepare or oversee the preparation of reports and statistics related to areas of responsibility
- Hire and oversee training and supervision of staff.
- Develop and implement schedules and procedures for safety inspections and preventive maintenance programs

EDUCATION

Computer Programming/Programmer, General

CPD - Seneca College • Graduated with Honours April 2020

SKILLS

- · Object Oriented Programming using Java, Kotlin, C# and C++
- Front-End Web Development using HTML/CSS/JavaScript, TypeScript, AngularJS
- Back-End Web Development using NodeJS and Express
- Database experience using NoSQL tools like MongoDB and MySQL tools like DB2 and Oracle
- · Cross-Platform App development using Ionic and Xamarin Forms
- · Native App Development using Android Studio

PROFESSIONAL CREDENTIALS

· Canadian Red Cross First-Aid Certificate

AWARDS AND HONOURS

Computer Programmer with Honours

2020

Completed Computer Programmer Program at Seneca with a cumulative 3.9 GPA

LINKS

- chriskelly48th.ca Personal Website with links and descriptions of work
- github.com/ckelly2112 Personal GitHub Page
- linkedin.com/in/ckellytor LinkedIn Page